

#### **About Me**

Diligent software craftsman that loves to do challenging tasks and learn new things with more than 13 years of experience in developing web based application in both Back-end and Front-end. quiet and hard worker. interested of doing challenging tasks and teamworking and remote working.

# Saeid Doroudi

**FullStack Web Developer** 

### **EXPERIENCE**

### 2019-06 - Now

Full Stack web and Mobile developer at Mobinnet Telecom

### 2018-05 - 2019-03

Mobile and Frontend Developer at ArtinMehr.

#### #2015-04 - 2019-03

Full Stack software developer at Elcaco.

#### #2014-07 - 2015-02

Co Founder and software developer at Balootsoft.

### #2008 - 2018

Freelancer Software developer and done projects for:

- Tabriz University
- Iran Army
- Hoopa publications
- Abna news agency
- Blogsky
- SahandZoob
- Marand Municipality
- And more

# AWARDS

1st place in 3rd congress of electronic content (eLearning) in solo section in Iran (2008).

# HOBBIES

Listen Podcast, Music, AudioBooks Football, Basketball, Biking Learn new things

### SALLARY

Requested salary is about 150,000,000 Rials per Month

### SKILLS

**ASP.Net Core, Asp.Net** 

C# and .Net BCL

**Design Patterns** 

Database Design and Solution architecting

**DDD-TDD** 

Clean Architecture

JS-ES6-TypeScript

HTML,CSS

Vue.Js - Vuex- Nuxt - Gridsome

Angular, AngularJs

SQL Server, NoSQL

REST API, GraphQL

**Automated Testing** 

WebPack, Parcel **Ionic Framework** 

**Bootstrap, TailwindCSS** 

Git, TFS, CI/CD

**OOP Concepts** 

Docker

**Microservice Concepts** 

**EF, Dapper** 

Flutter, Dart

AdobeXD, Figma

### **EDUCATIONS**

Bachelor of Software enginering technologies Daneshvaran University (Tabriz) 2013 Associate Degree of Software enginering technologies Tabriz University of Technology (Tabriz) 2011

# **EDUCATIONS**

Diploma in C# Programming (Alison) Diploma in HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript (Alison) Diploma in Web Business Development and Marketing (Alison) Diploma in Web Design (Alison)

JavaScript, CSS, Jquery, HTML, C#, Python 3, SQL, JAVA and ... courses at Sololearn

### CONTACTS

+989144786806

doroudi@live.com



yummycode.ir



doroudi



/users/5292901/saeid-doroudi